[
    {"question": "ア", "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "イ", "answer": "i"},
    {"question": "ウ", "answer": "u"},
    {"question": "エ", "answer": "e"},
    {"question": "オ", "answer": "o"},
    {"question": "カ", "answer": "ka"},
    {"question": "キ", "answer": "ki"},
    {"question": "ク", "answer": "ku"},
    {"question": "ケ", "answer": "ke"},
    {"question": "コ", "answer": "ko"},
    {"question": "サ", "answer": "sa"},
    {"question": "シ", "answer": "shi"},
    {"question": "ス", "answer": "su"},
    {"question": "セ", "answer": "se"},
    {"question": "ソ", "answer": "so"},
    {"question": "タ", "answer": "ta"},
    {"question": "チ", "answer": "chi"},
    {"question": "ツ", "answer": "tsu"},
    {"question": "テ", "answer": "te"},
    {"question": "ト", "answer": "to"},
    {"question": "ナ", "answer": "na"},
    {"question": "ニ", "answer": "ni"},
    {"question": "ヌ", "answer": "nu"},
    {"question": "ネ", "answer": "ne"},
    {"question": "ノ", "answer": "no"},
    {"question": "ハ", "answer": "ha"},
    {"question": "ヒ", "answer": "hi"},
    {"question": "フ", "answer": "fu"},
    {"question": "ヘ", "answer": "he"},
    {"question": "ホ", "answer": "ho"},
    {"question": "マ", "answer": "ma"},
    {"question": "ミ", "answer": "mi"},
    {"question": "ム", "answer": "mu"},
    {"question": "メ", "answer": "me"},
    {"question": "モ", "answer": "mo"},
    {"question": "ヤ", "answer": "ya"},
    {"question": "ユ", "answer": "yu"},
    {"question": "ヨ", "answer": "yo"},
    {"question": "ラ", "answer": "ra"},
    {"question": "リ", "answer": "ri"},
    {"question": "ル", "answer": "ru"},
    {"question": "レ", "answer": "re"},
    {"question": "ロ", "answer": "ro"},
    {"question": "ワ", "answer": "wa"},
    {"question": "ヲ", "answer": "wo"},
    {"question": "キャ", "answer": "kya"},
    {"question": "キュ", "answer": "kyu"},
    {"question": "キョ", "answer": "kyo"},
    {"question": "シャ", "answer": "sha"},
    {"question": "シュ", "answer": "shu"},
    {"question": "ショ", "answer": "sho"},
    {"question": "チャ", "answer": "cha"},
    {"question": "チュ", "answer": "chu"},
    {"question": "チョ", "answer": "cho"},
    {"question": "ニャ", "answer": "nya"},
    {"question": "ニュ", "answer": "nyu"},
    {"question": "ニョ", "answer": "nyo"},
    {"question": "ヒャ", "answer": "hya"},
    {"question": "ヒュ", "answer": "hyu"},
    {"question": "ヒョ", "answer": "hyo"},
    {"question": "ミャ", "answer": "mya"},
    {"question": "ミュ", "answer": "myu"},
    {"question": "ミョ", "answer": "myo"},
    {"question": "リャ", "answer": "rya"},
    {"question": "リュ", "answer": "ryu"},
    {"question": "リョ", "answer": "ryo"},
    {"question": "ティ", "answer": "ti"},
    {"question": "トゥ", "answer": "tu"},
    {"question": "ファ", "answer": "fa"},
    {"question": "フィ", "answer": "fi"},
    {"question": "フェ", "answer": "fe"},
    {"question": "フォ", "answer": "fo"},
    {"question": "ヴァ", "answer": "va"},
    {"question": "ヴィ", "answer": "vi"},
    {"question": "ヴェ", "answer": "ve"},
    {"question": "ヴォ", "answer": "vo"},
    {"question": "ギャ", "answer": "gya"},
    {"question": "ギュ", "answer": "gyu"},
    {"question": "ギョ", "answer": "gyo"},
    {"question": "ジャ", "answer": "ja"},
    {"question": "ジュ", "answer": "ju"},
    {"question": "ジョ", "answer": "jo"},
    {"question": "ヂャ", "answer": "ja"},
    {"question": "ヂュ", "answer": "ju"},
    {"question": "ヂョ", "answer": "jo"},
    {"question": "ビャ", "answer": "bya"},
    {"question": "ビュ", "answer": "byu"},
    {"question": "ビョ", "answer": "byo"},
    {"question": "ピャ", "answer": "pya"},
    {"question": "ピュ", "answer": "pyu"},
    {"question": "ピョ", "answer": "pyo"},
    {"question": "ウィ", "answer": "wi"},
    {"question": "ウェ", "answer": "we"},
    {"question": "ウォ", "answer": "wo"},
    {"question": "シェ", "answer": "she"},
    {"question": "チェ", "answer": "che"},
    {"question": "テュ", "answer": "tyu"},
    {"question": "ディ", "answer": "di"},
    {"question": "フュ", "answer": "fyu"},
    {"question": "ツァ", "answer": "tsa"},
    {"question": "ツィ", "answer": "tsi"},
    {"question": "ツェ", "answer": "tse"},
    {"question": "ツォ", "answer": "tso"},
    {"question": "キェ", "answer": "kye"},
    {"question": "ギェ", "answer": "gye"},
    {"question": "ヒェ", "answer": "hye"},
    {"question": "ビェ", "answer": "bye"},
    {"question": "ピェ", "answer": "pye"},
    {"question": "ン", "answer": "n"}
    ]